Friends, through this video we are going to know in detail about the
quarter 4 result of ICICI LB stock.  The
company has
shared its audited financial results.   Along
with that, the final dividend has been shared on equity shares at ₹7
which is a good news.
So let us know about its result.
This result which has been mentioned is
according to these lax.
Leaving aside the EPS value, the income we are getting to see in this quarter is Rs.
6618 crore 76 lakh,
which was Rs. 6610 crore 15 lakh in the previous quarter
and Rs. 5851
crore 17 lakh in the previous year, so if we look at it as per the previous quarter,
we are getting to see an increase in the income
and if we look at it as per the previous year
also, we are getting to
see an increase in the income, which is a
good thing.  Let us now
know about the expenses of the stock.  The
expenses that can be seen are Rs 672
crore 91 lakh, which
was Rs 639 crore 6 lakh in the previous quarter and Rs 5435
crore 25 lakh in the previous year.  As per the previous quarter,
we are going to
see a slight increase in expenses and as per the
previous year also,
we are going to see an increase in expenses
and if the expenses are high,
we will see its direct impact on the profit of the company.  Let us
check how much net
profit the company has earned in this quarter.  The
profit that we are seeing in this quarter is Rs
546 crore 56 lakh, which
was Rs 658 crore 76 lakh in the previous quarter and Rs 509 crore 59 lakh in the previous year.
So, if we look at the previous quarter,
we are seeing a big decline in the profit
and as per the previous year, we are
seeing a slight increase in the profit, the
impact of which we will definitely see on the stock value.
Friends, if you are watching the video for the first time,
please support the channel by subscribing to it.  Let us now
know about the EPS value of the stock.
Which EPS value was 13.14.  Now it has
reduced slightly to 10.89.